crizmo.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | CRIZMO

At Crizmo.com, we give prime importance to privacy of our visitors and take it seriously. Our Privacy Policy Page stated that how we collect and store personal information about our visitors (like you) and how we use this information and for what purpose.

It is the basic right of every internet user to provide them all these information.

  1. **How information is collected?**
  2. **What Kind of information is collected?**
  3. **What is done with information?**
  4. **What are Cookies?**
  5. **How to accept or reject cookies?**
  6. **What are possible technical risks?**

### 01\. How information is collected

Information are collected when visitor contact us through our Contact Form or when the visitors made comments on our post.

Crizmo.com also uses Statcounter.com to collect and analyze the traffic data on our site. This data help us to better understand what our visitors look for in Crizmo and what their interest is. Using this data, we try to improve our blog content according to your interest.

What Kind of information is collected?

Generally we collect the following sort of information when someone made comment or contact us:

  * Name
  * E-mail Address
  * Location
  * Web Address

Our third Party visitor tracking system collect information about the user preferences, internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), Location (country and City), type of browser, date/time stamp, referring site, analyze trends and track user’s movement around the blog. Other than this, no any personal information is collected.

All these information are non-sharable and use to improve the user experience.

### 02\. What We Do with this Information?

As stated earlier, we keep your data confidential to prevent spamming and only use this data to improve our site content according to our visitor’s preferences. Although the data which is publically accessible are your Profile Name and the Web Address. No E-mail Address shown to public.

### 03\. What are Cookies?

Cookie files are small pieces of data or a sort of information that are sent from websites and stored in your computer. Once Stored, Cookies will be sent for your system to our website server.

Other than Crizmo.com, some third Party advertisement sites like Google AdSense, store Cookies on your computer to serve you better and relevant ads according to your location and interest.

### 04\. What Does Cookies Have To Do With My Privacy?

Although Cookies are generally use for better user browsing experience, some Cookies (tracking cookies) tracks the user browsing habit, information about preferences and can track the record of user interest. Authentication cookies let the server or website know about whether the user is logged on or off.

  * **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.crizmo.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.crizmo.com

  * **Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on newyeargreeting2014.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.crizmo.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.crizmo.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

### 05\. How to accept or reject Cookies?

By default Cookies are accepted from all sites. To reject or disable Cookies,  you may go through your browser options. More details information about disabling cookies can be found at respective browser website

We don’t have any sort of control over the Cookies used by third party advertisers. You may personally change the preferences of advertisement or stop them from storing cookies by visiting Google Ads Privacy Policy and Go to Ad Setting at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### 06\. What are Potential Technical Risks?

We at Crizmo.com, make sure to keep confidential any sort of data being collected through our site or through third part visitor tracking system. We try best to keep and use your personal information sensibly and carefully. Technically there is no actual or potential harm or risk to privacy. **  
**  
Visiting Crizmo.com means that you are accepting our privacy policy and Terms & Conditions.

If you still have any query or concerns about our Privacy Policy, feel free to **[Contact Us](http://www.crizmo.com/contact-us)**. We are there to satisfy you and gain your trust.
